

phone 816.547.7758

e-mail nickcopelin@gmail.com web

nickcopelin.com

www.linkedin.com/in/nickcopelin

Professional Summary

Account Services and Client Engagement professional with 4+ years of success managing ocal and national clients in B2B and B2C relationships. Channel experience includes: digital, broadcast, radio, print, outdoor, direct mail, POP, SEM, and SEO.

Education

Missouri State University, May 2011 College of Business - AACSB accredited Bachelor of Science in Marketing with an emphasis in Advertising and Promotions Minor in Design

Professional Experience

Account Manager

January 2015 - Present

Salva O'Renick; Kansas City, MO

- · Demonstrate confidence and authority as the day-to-day voice of the agency team and main client contact
- · Accurately anticipate client needs, interpret requests, and initiate projects
- Plan and organize agency work, handling multiple projects efficiently and effectively, while balancing the dual expectations of clients and the agency
- Establish clear objectives and priorities for client initiatives and communicate them accurately with the agency and clients
- Work Help develop, articulate, and adhere to, agreed upon strategies to meet client goals and exceed KPIs
- · Skillfully present the agency's recommendations and creative products to client and agency decision-makers

Account Executive

October 2012 - Present

Salva O'Renick; Kansas City, MO

- Serve as client's first point of contact in managing and executing projects
- · Assist Account Director in coordinating and producing special projects for clients
- · Maintain weekly status reports and lead status meetings with clients and the agency
- Participate in the preparation of materials for promotional planning and new business presentations as needed
- Work in conjunction with creative and traffic to develop job estimates and timelines
- Client experience: Applebee's, Ameriprise Financial, Central Bancompany, sMissouri Employers Mutual, Lockton Companies, Protective Life Insurance, DST, GEHA, Charlie Hustle

Account Coordinator

July 2011 - May 2012

The Marlin Company; Springfield, MO

- Assisted with various research projects
- Routed projects internally
- · Populated and distributed insertion orders
- Updated schedules and media calendars
- Client experience: Starbucks, Bush Brothers Beans, Blue Bunny, Unilever. Splenda, and Sweet Street Desserts

phone 816.547.7758

e-mail nickcopelin@gmail.com

web nickcopelin.com

www.linkedin.com/in/nickcopelin

Internship Experience

Taco Bell Campus Marketing Representative Williams/Crawford Marketing; Fort Smith, AR

August 2010 - May 2011

- Acted as liaison to 15,000+ students
- · Coordinated sponsorships for organizations and campus-wide events
- · Set in motion numerous promotional deals, games, contests, and campaigns
- Developed, maintained, and utilized Facebook, Twitter, and Foursquare pages for promotional efforts

Marketing Intern May 2010 - August 2010

Breakthrough Marketing+Design+Technology; Kansas City, MO

- Coordinated models, prepared inventory, and assisted in multiple photo shoots
- · Assisted with search engine optimization and SEMs campaigns
- Designed and populated template websites
- Proofread and edited two 80+ page catalogues

VP of Publicity July 2009 - May 2010

Student Activities Council of Missouri State; Springfield, MO

- Oversaw a 6 person executive board in charge of student programming and a \$262,000 budget
- Utilized an \$11,000 budget for planning events and SAC publicity
- Created innovative advertising schemes and promotions utilizing grass roots and guerilla marketing techniques
- Directed a 15 person committee to create, implement, and distribute publicity

Core Competencies:

- · Account management
- Project management
- · Oral and written communication
- Relationship management
- Organization
- · Social media
- · Content marketing
- Process improvement
- · Attention to detail
- · Problem solving
- · Herding cats

Technical Proficiencies:

- · Microsoft Office Suite
- · Adobe Creative Suite
- Google Business Applications
- Social Media Management and Measurement Tools
- Project Management Tools